

PAUL M HERMAN

303 Willowbay Ridge St. Sanford, FL 32771 (C) 407-414-5903 | pmherman85@icloud.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/paul-m-herman-cpht-86280536

Professional SummaryAn organized, detail-oriented, and conscientious self-starter, able to strategize and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks and stay calm under pressure, while being an experienced supervisor and trainer; able to explain information clearly, recognize excellence in individuals, and inspire team members to achieve their potential while working toward common goals and grow within an organization.

Work History

Store Manager

Walgreens Boots Alliance

Mar 2014 - Current Longwood, FL

- Worked with over 100 Assistant Store Manager Trainees and Shift Leads to achieve new leadership for company.
- Analyzed department documents for appropriate distribution and filing.
- Obtained documents, clearances, certificates and approvals from local, state and federal agencies.
- Managed high volume pharmacy
- Increased store income by \$300,000 YoY
- Increased store level engagement and performance.
- Analyze business statements to create effective business plans to improve store performance and customer experience.
- Payroll management, scheduling, cash management, merchandising, time management.
- Managed both hourly and overtime exempt employees, between 25 50 employees at one time.

Assistant Store Manager/Executive Asst. Manager

Walgreens Boots Alliance

May 2010 - Mar 2014 Orlando, FL

Drug Store Management Trainee

Walgreens Boots Alliance

Various other positions within the company since 2003: Service Clerk, Photo/Head Photo Specialist

Apr 2003 - May 2010

Orlando, FL

Education

Full Stack Coding Boot Camp

University of Central Florida

2018 Sanford, FL

Orlando, FL

2016

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

University of Phoenix

Emphasis in Networking Coursework in Professional Prospecting Skills

Coursework in Speech and Communication, Sociology and Psychology

Associate's Degree: General Studies, Information Technology

Coursework includes Business Management, Finance and Accounting

Certified Pharmacy Technician

Pharmacy Technician Certification Board

2012 (Current and Active)

Registered Pharmacy Technician

Florida Department of Health

2010 (Current and Active)

Volunteer Organizations

- American Heart Association
- Red Nose Day American Diabetes Association
- Nathaniel's Hope
- Skills
 - Budgeting and finance
 - Project Management
 - Project Leadership
 - Self-motivated Strong verbal communication
 - Conflict resolution
 - Extremely organized
 - Team leadership
 - Process implementation
 - Staff development
 - Large computer networks
 - Retail pharmacy operations knowledge
 - Pharmacy automation

 - Typing speed 100 WPM
 Regional level facilitation, coaching and training
 - Peer development

- City of Longwood
- GR8TODON8 Organ Donation
- · Cystic Fibrosis Foundation
 - Networking within communities for community events, brand awareness, and volunteering
 - Knowledgable with Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Premiere, Indesign)
 - Knowledgable with Macintosh and Windows based systems
 - Proficient with Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel and Access
 - HTML5, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, AJAX, Firebase, PHP, SQL